it's a really really nice that's a
session Thank You Stanley
[Applause]
[Music]
towards the end of the morning we all
get tired I'm Anderson we're fund
important for trucks anemic I'm Shenouda
die Hinton taught me I thought we'd have
some fun
keep talking about negative emotions
instead of a negativity lets us play
Indian step receive MA why don't we go
to the review and then welcome back to
depression this isn't feel afraid for
his team andand ambition beyond
speedometer awesome ending of the review
of the last eight years of either be a
beer me it's not my D let's not got it
decide to get your master's degree as a
went to dine and then I talked to our
lumber in math um Proust eras those of
you who don't decide to become an RM
teacher-didi kindly revered voices what
similarly fry and all that I said ACI
Lera so we're on Tim we're on item 81
listen by Eden I know doctor 81 my
non-toxic and you probably have it it's
a it's a glass flower this is I need
blue males real ass page aim of the site
I asked okay I'm gonna start explaining
it and then the kids in the tech table
will figure it out
I'm historian so it's a glass
flower design it blew my house flowers
like customer in a big common sensation
they're hard to keep clean right the
same sri Eric's Albert so high
even emotionally and they break easily
uncie break now of life so what it means
is that is the long rim rating we didn't
reach the long room especially but a
slambien talking about the introduction
it's a mnemonic but what it means is I
like to collect your spiritual real
estate its diameter - LS your mind
sliced very very precious my guys to
save share cost button kappa oh a bunny
three times ice to this link on topics
dualistic cup of the mind you carry all
the table and guys custody can set aside
to buy her a new in snakes deliveries to
have seen us in 4k language on the phone
see try Alice I used to dream about the
Starbucks all the time
it's fine stop curry
happiness and I was a pretty common
dream of tantrayana the first six months
are quite difficult on the essence more
necessary Eric
staying in one room as a shriek the guns
inside in animal design it's a snake
time and we were in a different part of
this desert we were over those mountains
we have on I'll try to get back as far
as all Salma has been no one's ever
lived there naman Tata you must walking
on this fire sadly there were very
strange animals Berkeley feeling fear
there there's one that looks like a
lobster cooked a guy synodical dousman
hormone you meditate they used to crawl
up on you made it had sewn zinzie Bimini
crap the Dakota House informal kind
scorpion Sun and sucrose
there's a called SunSpider nuggets off
the Sun in spin Edison they like so like
meditators on de Medici are like that
one day we had we had a lot of
rattlesnakes we had five rattlesnakes
you have now Felix long-term yeah hi my
son's clapper schlong and I hope this
time I got on the fence 20 pin often
sound it letter push one out oh my
name's Wilfred Bion hibiki sentai second
I know old aunt a mere misdemeanor I
wish to confess tight not too tight but
after six months about a six month from
quiet - still there you can talk to
animals
consummate tiaras very cool I'm talking
for six months unless they're at Diamond
Mountain for a three-year retreat as I
mention your knee off sex no not at all
our Ruby steam fire a little smaller
than fat round it may be a common disk
off your course for six months on vendor
sex one on each database you can start
to understand them I'm fresh taste to
see so we had lots of cool animals day
you did not come in a high-pitched sound
and then we had a pet rabbits don't
happen via highest not communion that
became very close friend the monkey
Freud and I'm sleep more meeting hey
exactly avoid the short arms and a
turkey club or cookies okay can you get
a cookie one day I was so I didn't have
a toilet having Heinen toilet that I can
boss I had a kinda electricity so I have
to poop outside as I'm will see human
rights I need to try you know those
bombing planes they have to try to drop
the bomb in the correct place
so I had a plastic bag and I said Ken
Schrader's each must am i indeed in the
plastic boy/girl trade the bag for my
food unhappy boy taking my it's not our
skit hushed cause and effect
I'm pooping on my bag outside well then
happy Strauss better to keep your poop
outside in my name point lesser the
pointless trousers Ryan and the rabbit
came and hit my leg ha finances habits
granite side from it just kind of side
there cakes came in my vitae
and minun I don't talk I just called I'm
a nun mind buying he stole he dug a hole
right mr. Godsey and Laura wanted me to
watch digging a hole yeah I could get
sued us to unlock grapes then then he
spread his legs over the hole and then
hot define it but then I had the bottom
loss all right so that's my baby's given
worn in the slaw Oh your girl and then
she take grass that's how scaredy-baby
escalate them sit for about five days
under massive circles I can make basic
booted the coyote can smell on Toyotas
region current only babies just kind of
say what that Canadians I never have a
good the city vaccean Dinah stock is why
smoke comes to then the common Austin
lost by one column is the one the same
way by the keyboards in the organizers
as the own one who ruined our s
competition these digits wire is
enormous
I come in here on a book about it I
didn't publish it
he kept on bugging me up so nice because
after a while you start to suspect there
are little buddhas my leggings thanks to
the sikh lining put us in very versatile
anyway anyway why did I talk about that
autumn hobbits the sits at sealed I
forgot completely oh yeah
in the after six months night bored you
can't meditate how they forget it
constantly stinking start Medici
indistinctl its kinks or Oh Monty rirs
retreat about a safari kismet is his
eyes you know it was very hard as I say
hi you could hear by yoga has to come
doctor dog dog me - rice are interrupt
but we found out something cool cool is
Ross if you can watch movies in the
minute had shown consideration for film
editor for nationalist we have lousy a
timeline when do also you mustn't wine
in guys my ski scene has to Alice's in
tandem guys the office I hear those
impressions are there DCI all the people
start to get for forgetful this a global
dimensions that Leslie well the the
plaintiff all is I told John Brady
there's a test for Alzheimer's I kept on
period centers and testified a time you
can't remember what Alzheimer's means
you have it finished by xiah time is
sunrise to us you can't fit in watch a
movie okay why am I talking about the
consequence it's not done fencing class
human suit on in your life unless he
died namely when the off gets rise new
dynamic guys Alice everything you hear I
less less to her and it takes that part
of your mind on the sets you hi - guys
this hard drive
that the I have lots of spec runs
towards the end of your life I'm anti
nicely I guess I'm falling raised when
you died on the globe is what we lurched
we feel the fundamental steps and thanks
widow Fonfon ion but what you learn in a
three-year retreat my priority be
careful save for you to listen to bust
okay like when you have a choice about
which teaching to go to when the divine
hostage Italy for Craig because you know
yesterday I said you don't have time God
you know what happened that's one
problem that's my problem that's the
title of the meeting but the other thing
is you Norman Alice us to Hearst but off
key moment so in the lamb rim in llama
room at the beginning got some sales
pitch for that fancy how
they say choose your teachings wisely
really tiny four treasures Italian saya
saya by okay don't go to every teaching
gimme stout in three because stay with
you that live by do not for one life
we finally amongst Italy so when you go
to hear some I don't know dumb New Age
psychology last year's popular I so
green and forth I guess this let's tips
you who Luka she is so tiara she was
very strong in Flagstaff and comes by
loitering they got stuck in the snow
storm I found them a place to stay
deeply more than happy not tell foresee
before we got a car full of ayahuasca
you want some Shaba know I made a
mistake
what's that hakima I
I said yeah I thought okay
hyah thing do I want this in my mind I'm
fragile
okay this last house day long and Adam
guys material it records everything
that's why I see this thing constantly
are asymmetry so be careful so for any
thing lightly everything in here and
it's like fatigue on who analysis women
common life for many innocent guys are
along behind photographers house along
so do you really wanna watch youtube
video about the cats jumping this
affected us you know you want kinda long
son you do you want these guys shooting
people in your mind mr. Fixit
greetings ethical but I know your real
estate accessory line dine
toy sensitive it will record everything
on this site for sequels your mind okay
be picky you know checkout teachers I've
a lavish is a four-time well and Freund
get you
nam joke about what is that yeah it
means geek mister run right it means
young means run after teachers
because somebody said it was cool okay
they look handsome number 81 your mind
is like a glass flower is beautiful and
your - my pleasure
be careful right you because who you let
in your mind who you will let come into
your mind be careful you don't have
space for many people and whatever they
gonna teach you is gonna be there for a
thousand Alice for city of vibration so
do what you watch on the internet things
like that okay really want that in your
mind in am 82 I'm gonna stop in 15
minutes okay 10 15 you take a no PP
bring maybe even a son nevermind okay
intimating - it's a pet peeve of mine
Marsha even spy on the Asik is my
favorite one of my favorite irritations
okay and so on so in Arizona I grew up
in Arizona we moved here I was born in
Los Angeles I came here you need a car
bye ray Elmas here she started three
jewels 3 to 30 are good and that's where
we taught the first a solution I'd like
to thank her
and she has many good qualities but one
she doesn't have said Fela Kuti Aisha
decides you guess yet
we tried we tried yeah I'm sorry hit so
many cactuses opposite sophie alekan in
brief this is Alton okay then you know
my friends hit du/dr because you have to
drive Arizona the plexus in Sioux riders
Ananda you have we'd learned to drive
when we're 15 we learn and out of
fundamental photo and the Shuler my
friends would say gala found a good deal
unlike what they say I got a cheap tires
I found some cheap but they're like $15
I'm gonna save like $50 happy so quickly
and I'm like done alright Shawna so
that's why you drive right yesterday on
society because things are so far apart
it's two hours to get to Tucson to a
real grocery store it's right here
omatsu comment so I said what's the
speed limit on highway 10 here 36 and
100 okay I understand it's a lot of km/h
it's modern come on yeah 110 okay
it's fast it should be highly sacred for
this one that's one secret RV - okay you
have to join and then Arizona lives most
of its far after Autobahn lifeblood
system
so question for you state the $50
I'm like yeah yeah why are we talking
about that you look at high school right
in front of my friends car I know you
made it had sort of fun not so much a
sign that our relativity you understand
that in five minutes and since we know
what you can plant a seed in your mind
car accident
being a going to ohio Oscar ceremony
something like that I don't want to call
me ceremony meditation no a minute
Etzion no it's a car accident is this
you know change your life for the rest
of you even though the intelafone don't
think looking for bringing in a foolish
teaching
now the stagnant blood was like a car
accident it's my mother
like thousand-yard stepmother - Steve
Mota she when my father died when I was
about 20 sessions never married Jeanne
Freudian then she was on a cruise you
know like long shots trying to get me to
do with the Penguins that would be nice
to have a husband and someone's medicine
and have-nots period as I get older I
was a sign medica it and then it turned
out he was not what she thought you see
well then happy heroes until he was in
his money all day all day day and
optimises very I think Anson hug
fancying it cook and it was difficult
for her five years or something she
found out not some fee on he was she had
asked if one that's Price Waterhouse
care home I did miss appearing to be
hiding so what a name Lara valiente's
son just got a they're very big company
edge not be careful as when on what
Rockhurst safe for you open your mind to
safe for cystic was like movies are the
same also meant
very good my partner Veronica she she
will often walk out of a movie but only
cast it off now since its kind of browse
difficult for me
because I'm like should I walk out or
not not necessary for me to believe in
Soul man my baby that's lady - okay big
mistake this is teaching the sportrack
basu which you haven't checked it out go
ahead and approve toss it's just for fun
that's fairly leave by the assign or
something without thinking much like
looking at your phone so this mean or
not so paying me off their telephone so
everything you have done to sleep
through Indian Alice was to versus all
right mama dry on the act there were
some people you know like in the
monastery you here monks caches
candidates young in Gloucester has to
feel a you may occasionally rise they
will say I don't I don't want to go to
alarm M decisions come got a llamas it's
not part of the guess she is the stylist
Keshi Keshi of course you only get alarm
em when you have a visiting teacher and
guess it was us not slamming when I know
the candidates will say some lamrim gain
that's for the guys who can't do the
guessing this is for the still against
gimmicks and on the gash it costs they
put down the alarm in the and then Papa
Wemba che got really irritated people
negative guys you cannot succeed in
Buddhism that comes the final dinah
praxis is Sigma meeting guys they won't
succeed just practice
Beth diamante corrected Giancana profs
the slum room it's the engine that
drives the car is this remote auditing
car at us out one needed to
other people okay so we're in this
system we are following the rules I
didn't want I don't care
okay so why are we doing this cuz maybe
you want to be specialized in learning
like or maybe you just want to get
enlightened life history on our oyster
okay some lower motivation
okay NM 84
it'll feel - sick this is tricky
this is difficult for you okay so I
don't think this is the last thing I'll
take a break Hausa who invented the
lamrim so people and you say when did
lahrman start in you know Artesia
Artesia got a job from his teacher right
Sergey Alphonse I'm Laramie call my name
is time a donkey the it's like when
Rinpoche sent me to New York
here's a diamond cutter Sutra good luck
Mahan chest is a much lighter Sutra yeah
so sages text say she takes there's a
Scottish people here say this text is a
text they all want to quit their text
and say geez Ali I'm done this ages
things ma can disrupt the message on how
to open your heart be mundus hats earth
net and after we started his text
assignment text is this and water column
realize it had a lot of tantor in it
decided it was okay but he's a llama and
she and she's not in a hyper slum
rebstock
so if you ask people who started the
Longmen son shootin attrition activity
chic that's when alarm start islamic
onin what was the name of our teachers
little army was Vietnam if on a t-shirt
sky name Lemuria what ya body butter
pradipika water partner but
pick a lamp on the path to enlightenment
okay baby beautiful what's a slap on
session we should learn it beside miss
lannen so people will say lahrman
started there
Alice I thought object.observe
999 so what who who started the Norman
Lord Buddha had the slammer Mb :
and for $100 $400
okay I gotta make it a little difficult
I was a bit century attic from a lien
why does the name of the alarm improve
it must have been taught by the Buddha
varoom device tanaami lamrim this is fun
boot achillea via raise your hand I'm
not giving away money to anyone who
shouts it psyched
Oh you don't get it that's why I should
get a kickback but if you don't get it
right it's all it means I wondered if I
shan't what gift what's first of all
what's the name what is the knowledge of
what we're studying yeah good Alstom
fascinating nice yeah the speed or
demons can't teach dolphin yamunda
c-store from drowning
okay perfect if a monkey hits a
typewriter all day man and one word will
come on affair awesome keep our tiptoes
I think it's what's up I yeah perfect
it's Sigma also Islam in the namitha
slam rims steps to Buddhahood Buddha
shaft I saw you're gonna write that way
I can describe it yeah
focus get really upset Lanka who studied
the lamb who started the path understand
okay so if somebody ask you as a vendor
human frog who's teaching very here's
the answer in the item it says
Here I am a domestic goddess own the
piace is shine lamrim causes violence
therefore the percentage often
enlightenment become somebody's money
who wrote the map to do so about who
started them kind at the baths Viviane
deep in mud bottom sucked if you got a
hot dog I'll risk another hundred why
does it say deep in wine bottoms like
the Stifel slow down
chief grand I can't fight good which is
which yeah deepest teachings on
emptiness chief is Cindy LeAnn nobody
laid eyes on Dwight teachings on Cindy
Lee got it hundred dollars he's got to
no wait no he's got a hundred he's gonna
phone dad yeah I guess
okay I've kind of given fifty cuts only
more okay alright so there's two great
lineage I skipped spike Rosaleen Ian
inside the lamb room in Lamoure if you
say it's simply hiding for house they're
called see highs too hard on white deep
tea in white on white which is in
Buddhism describes the ocean to the
ocean factly we often compare Buddhism
to those but this most but off MIT
immediately so there's two great men
ages I'll skip cycles he goes down to
the bottom and then wide lie it takes
time to fly from China to start that
sideline from Kenan on Californians who
flee those intense they wouldn't
teachings on Lamont White
one teeth sandelion okay those are
specific lineages
vegetable oil their hands upon see what
vitamin C fish boy tomorrow okay yeah
Mon flows other flows close fast we okay
I'll teach you American idiom March are
you ready no cigar nice some ancient
game is lovely when you get a cigar like
it's oh oh I don't skate off 99 thrown
aback I need Sagara to other lineages
you got both bye-bye Bahamas bodhichitta
only a hot you are
understood you should pay me huh
he already said that what no ok in the
lamrim tradition in the entire cylinder
practices me I'm thanking you it's like
that means the lineage of personal
practice delineated a CI it's kind of a
CI a patient modules its own little
minions module any praxis module a
Tomlin how to meditate human made it
seems like that personal six times
especially sex my personal practice
practicum in the lamrim uh third lineage
that's but I still in deep inside and in
labrum because of the for drugs is
linear the Fiat is pleased ek hai many
leaders for I said Vicki forestry yeah
man
rim of abundance and compassion stream
Mitka food emptiness stream yeah hi
normally the practice stream in those
paintings is put in the middle the
mileage I see but I think in lamrim
guilt sits on copies left you have
wisdom links for some cars always live
eyesight well somebody Lincoln had some
copies right Einar if'n law doesn't
pursue him okay questions we have about
15 minutes any questions no questions
Kenneth Hagen I have a question for you
given if I get for a what's the three
ways to become the most popular ACI
teacher they give you to the Philip
believe the state's al Abedin counts
number one no man's know your material
wait retina has a question she has a
microphone action itself especially
often
Vitalik Dindo in new york in favor gay
game has the same hopeful tone the
signature christian can be like
goddesses exist yet well the saddam was
so my so exist in very basic Christian
can today Lincoln the rash the tale
that's tough
I'm still gonna write a buncha give her
a birthday and she kept aloof this many
months I can have a certificate function
yet yeah had meat never means been photo
like you had the skirt and Donna justice
two-tiered the punk debunked in any
first encounter and then ethnicity
encounter are given analog gear and when
a linear from Latin host with the
already Hindi heightened
when electricity to exceed wicked and
has to know the Lincoln Health Day on th
they're healthy and the Bavarian and
electricity get to that the truthful
honest except the attentive to know this
comes from an explanation that we had in
venerable Bastian it questions this all
of our the idea the individual some
bleep up it's it's just today everything
we think we're okay not just car keys
and things like that so at least charter
because we grew up with car keys and
light switches it's extremely difficult
this is also a pragmatic way of thinking
of my suit why did the light go on llama
pelmet turned them why did the cars and
it's it's built into us this component
mistake okay for selfish and until we
understand it it's bittersweet e15 we
won't really change and it was a mistake
he feigned and kind of like Kazan least
get on when you turn the switch unit in
Shia because you gave light doing other
people in the pattern though it has
nothing to do with this will help okay
I'm sure that's it on okay
guests are you saying the light switch
yes are you saying yes in the car key
doesn't start that hot that's okay
guests are you saying sometimes you can
start this car without okay starting
customers yes yeah saying that okay so
are you saying sometimes you have a key
in the carton started yeah okay so
in in in higher middle way when you turn
the key nothing touches anything else
okay
it's not possible electricity circuit
closes so this the way I was taught in
high school I don't know how they did
now I suspect it's a little loose balls
tennis balls in the wire copper wire
says Dave it's this Adam hits this and
then charge comes out the other end of
the wire so the atoms like a billiard
ball so this atom hits this atom and
then that has its own it has to be like
that right somehow turned economy
completely and that closes the circuit
okay and then closes the circuit and
then the balls start hitting each other
beginning pushes power and really if you
want to get radical into ecologist it's
a deeper religion you can say I'm
Buddhist you can really we're all at
myself owners you see the and the deeply
held belief of this world stuff is made
you see it's a deeply held belief and as
long as we believe so guests are go back
to the atom and I have trouble teaching
it and I felt it when I was in New York
to Lynn you know I just got it from a
translation and I said oh this is a good
present
so I know how you feel like it helps it
doesn't solve the you can't use clay
doesn't carry electricity only if it's
copper but you can't string gold wires
all over the country in India with the
unions this ball hits the ball he's
about to lift off tonight it has to be a
in the metal group of the periodic chart
of the elements
it has to be a metal basically it came
is more of diamond to carry electricity
and well it has to be it has mr. Muhsin
has have a certain number of electron
and proton Lehtonen and neutral okay and
those you know in the model which is
just a model not necessary that's it
those are arranged in shells around and
then there's a shell shy electrons and
then it has a charge the point is that
structure of the tennis ball then this
has to be exactly that you know so sore
it's not copper anymore I mean if you
close hydrogen atom
sorry Vashta filament or and yeah if you
pull a hydrogen atom it's become
something else T it changes to healing
or not that doesn't work anymore so okay
so if you take anything out of the shell
it's not gonna die these copper anymore
and it won't for carry so it has to be
protons in the model in the modular
right now the reason chef moment sent so
those electrons this vigil II see and
the protons individually are generic
seen an electron atom is the same as an
electron in another animal spirit in a
shell of oxygen
it's the same as the electron in itself
in a shell of copper in there okay those
healers are not different those are just
positive negative oh you see it I mean
if you could take you can take such
tremendous noise I mean they're not
proper electrons places are totally the
same
it's how you mix them together Auggie's
you'll make a copper okay or the visage
to feel which means the spirited if you
only make contact with like one electron
okay in a copper and pewter synonym Kufa
it's not going to work
then kind of sneeze function here
because it's the same as if you can only
make contact with the outer shell that
has a solemn acts that electron is not
different they are generic you see all
atoms are the same hailey arrangement
that electron is it substantial doesn't
have can you split an electron the next
one okay you can that's what that's what
colliders are force why they make ten
billion dollar certainty that's why they
make these things okay the pregnancy
electrons
okay which mean that trans weights be
directed and that electron has a right
side and side okay God in my okay so far
now yes when two copper atoms meet okay
you turn the switch right and then the
light goes on it's supposed to be tennis
balls copper atoms hit the next amended
charge came out of into the tungsten of
the line okay
supposed to be like that that assumes
that there's a left side on the right
side to the copper with me if the tennis
ball tennis if the whole first tennis
ball touches the whole second then
there's no movement because they're in
the same if Stanley hugs Allison Stanley
listen let me make sure this is gonna
work
and he tried if he tried to make every
inch of his skin touch every inch of her
skin the only way is if they were
standing in the same space you can check
it out we can hug is their way to hug
each other that you touch everywhere
only if you're in the state of and
emboss you see I mean what that means is
stay with me okay terrible thing to do
at the end I got what that means is if
all the copper atom made contact with
all the next comprehend there would be
no movement of electricity because it
would all be in the same space that
means they'd have to be in the same
bottle at home that's the only way for
all their skin to make contact with all
this get started on this a little bit
okay so it must be there for that only a
part of this Penhale
the front part touches the Beagle of the
next tenant portal this next antenna
spice period wet Spiegel bottom ass I
mean a polite word is okay so the front
side of this 10-foot I said that this
has to hit that ass okay the front end
of this not all of this ball can touch
all of this pocket because apparently
can't there for a season only some other
ante
right of the atom this is only some of
the electrons in some of the shells can
make contact with some of the shells
some of the electrons in the next on the
front side only has certain electrons in
that shell this atom of copper only has
electrons
some electrons in the bag and some
electrons in the front right
because they have the width because you
can split them in a Collider listening
therefore not all of the first atom of
copper is working for touch the copper
if all the elements for the electrons in
the first element governments are not
involved it cannot be copper Candace new
person and it cannot carry electricity
it's impossible what's happening but
when you turn your lights it's not
possible don't say suck me it's weird or
don't say it's I'm what I'm saying is to
think that the light goes on because she
turns to switch it's profound
misunderstanding again if it's profound
think that your husband will stop if you
talk to him event to globe the stay it's
profound misunderstanding of the world
and it's too big to talk about it at
11:01 okay but everything Alice you
think about what makes anything happen
it's completely falling fudge okay
completely okay it's not that
hard as Stephen Hawking is wrong and
tell from all of given satisfies so her
husband I told you this don't husband's
a publisher he asked me what's my next
I'm gonna prove Stephen Hawking's
rawness to focus he was feeling
conflicted because he published this
Stephen Hawking let's continue later
okay this method okay I promise a
question from Norbert first thing in the
evening no but then if I go this is
about pounds with engagement yeah
froggen abend okay good would you lead
the Mandela okay you wanna try
this sushi sasha has this you say what
you do okay in this is how an American
so she's not she and then the second
part you go okay got it
she met all time daddy son gash in do
make
lucky local number in the two pi he dumb
luck de chelly sort Ocean tsunami a
shallot your way my cool thank you for
working so hard
thank you this is so hot